keycode.com 2019-10-04

# Keycode: Our Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 14, 2018

Keycode is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our site's visitors. You can visit our website and browse the pages on our site without disclosing your name, e-mail address, log-in, password or any other type of personally identifiable information.

If you elect, as so many of you do, to participate in our mailing list created to alert you to new promotion codes for any or all of our retailers, you will give us, and we will store, your email address only. According to the parameters you set, you will be alerted from time to time of new discounts by email. You may opt out of this service at any time by responding to the directions to opt out at the bottom of the email you receive. We do not send regularly scheduled e-mails, such as monthly emails. We only contact you if we have something important to say.

If you choose to provide us with your email address we will not rent, share, or sell your e-mail address to any third party under any circumstances.

**Cookies** : A cookie is a tiny data file that contains a unique identification number that is transferred from any web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site can identify unique visitors to the site and track users' activities on the web site. Keycode uses cookies but their use does not tell us any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address or email address.

We collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies. For example, we may collect information from the devices you use to access our Services, your operating system type or mobile device model, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. Browsers routinely send these types of information to web servers. Our server logs also record the IP addresses of the devices you use to interact with the Services. We may also collect information about the website you were visiting before you came to our Services and the website you visit after you leave our Services, if this information is supplied to us by your browser.

**Links on Keycode** : Since the nature of Keycode is to provide discount information for use on other web sites, we provide links to hundreds of retailer web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and encourage you to review the privacy policies of those sites before given them your personal information.

**Security** : Keycode keeps technical, electronic, physical and other safeguards in place to protect both our system and any personal information we may hold. If you would like to contact our Privacy Officer, you can [initiate contact here](https://www.keycode/contact-us/). Please set forth the nature of your request or concern and provide the Privacy Officer with a way to contact you.

**Updates to Privacy Policy** : From time to time, Keycode reviews its privacy policies and procedures to ensure they remain current.

**Privacy Practices of Third Parties** : This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by Keycode through your interaction with the Services. Other websites that may be accessible through links from our Services may have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. Merchants and business partners may have their own privacy statements, too. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by these other parties prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** : From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to clarify our practices or to reflect new or different privacy practices, such as when we add new features to our Services. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. Your continued access or use of the Services after any such changes become effective constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as revised. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices.

**Children's Privacy** : Keycode does not intend that any portion of the Services will be accessed or used by children under the age of thirteen, and such use is prohibited. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least thirteen years old and understand that you must be at least thirteen years old in order to create an account and purchase the goods or services advertised through the Services. We will promptly delete information associated with any account for which we obtain actual knowledge that the registered user associated with the account is not at least thirteen years old.
